

Simutina Yelizaveta

Front-end developer

- O Ukraine
- **\(+380991184971**
- @ simutina.liza2003@gmail.com
- https://github.com/LissaSim

Certifications

JavaScript + React

Udemy Academy

2023-10-03

Languages

English

B1

Education

National Metallurgical Academy of

Ukraine

Student 3rd year

Projects

FS2S

November 2023- Present

https://fs2s-eight.vercel.app/

Skills

JavaScript

Css

HTML

React

Redux

TypeScript

Profiles

Oneliza

Telegram

Summary

I completed the course 'Advanced JavaScript + React' on Udemy. During the course, I familiarized myself with the basic syntax of JavaScript, and as I progressed through the lessons, I deepened my knowledge. Throughout the course, I worked with async JavaScript, HTTP requests, APIs, the DOM, and JSON data format. I also studied the React + Redux library and worked with both class components and hooks. In my GitHub repository, you can find projects that I worked on independently, as well as projects completed during the course. The 'TeamChallenge' project is an experience similar to a commercial project, based on a community for junior developers called TeamChallenge, where beginners work on their projects (currently, the project is in the development stage). After this course, I learned TypeScript.

Experience

Coffee service

Admin

My responsibilities included customer communication, issuing and receiving coffee machines for repairs, order management and logistics for deliveries

Coffee house

Barista

I communicated with customers and prepared various beverages, as well as took and processed orders

TeamChallenge

Front-end developer

November 2023 - Present time

2021-06-23 - 2022-02-21

2022-03-25 - 2023-02-17

On this project, I was responsible for the front-end development. I made requests to the back-end, integrated them with the page layout, implemented error handling, and application logic